♪ Oh, Mr. Tailor ♪
["Mr. Tailor" playing]
♪ Holding the scissors ♪
♪ One cut, and it's over ♪
Atoy is Ibyang's real father.
You're a fake mother?
Something like that, yes.
[in English] If you don't want anything
to happen to the woman and child,
you will tell me!
[in English] Where is the laptop?!
[in English] Do you want to know
where the laptop is?
[Atoy, in English] I need
proof of life first.
[grunts]
[in English] Who is the mother?
I don't know.
The only one who really mattered
to him was Audrey.
[Emerson] Oh, then maybe Ibyang
is also Audrey's child.
[imitate fighting sounds]
- Take it.
- [straining]
PREVIOUSLY
- [Ibyang] Hello?
- [Atoy on the phone] Ibyang?
Ibyang, this is Atoy.
Tatoy?!
I-- I-- I was captured.
[Atoy on the phone] Call my boss, Mercado.
Call him, tell him where I am.
Eh-- Eh, okay, Tatoy.
- Just trust, please.
- [sobs]
They will save us.
[Cita] Atoy is alive?
What else did he say?
He said he needs help
because he was captured.
[gasps]
He said he's at--
In Bulacan.
With Viktor Petrov.
[Audrey] So, he's being held
by the ambassador of Zahran!
He said we should find his boss, Mercado!
As in Jennylyn Mercado?
Do you know this man?
He often hangs out
at the basketball court.
- [man 1] Maybe he's there.
- That's Gavin!
I saw Daddy's men. They're looking for us.
♪ Fix it ♪
Karla, hasn't Atoy come home yet?
My God, I hope not.
Why, Miss Siony?
There's been so much violence here.
And isn't there that blond hoodlum
looking for him?
What if…
What if he got caught by that guy?
[Siony] And then, there's Emerson.
Just when they got close,
he got dragged into it.
His shop was burned!
That's not a coincidence.
That's why I'm always ready.
I always carry this.
Oh my, Miss Siony,
you've had too much coffee.
You're too nervous and alert!
But, hey, maybe Miss Siony has a point.
Oh, no. That means
Emerson might disappear too.
Oh, no! That can't be!
We're not even together yet.
You know, Denden, you should court him.
Because nothing will happen
if you don't make the move, girl.
[Jona] Yes!
[Emerson] Karla, did you see Uno?
Do you have his number?
Eh, Brother, no, but we met earlier.
I'll just check
if he's at the barbecue stall.
If you see him,
tell him to go to Atoy's shop.
Tell him it's important.
- I'll update you. All right, brother.
- Yes.
Oh. Emerson, Denden has something
to tell you before it's too late.
- [in English] Go.
- Uh…
- [Emerson] Ah.
Uh… It's about… my debt to Brother Kurt!
Yes. I'll give it to you instead.
But I didn't bring my wallet.
Wait, I'll just go back for it, okay?
- Okay.
- [indistinct]
[Jona] Oh, no.
I know that guy.
He looks like the one
who burned down your shop.
[in English] Oh my god, neighbors!
The arsonists are here!
There they are! There he is!
- There! Yes!
- [gasps]
‪[suspicious music playing]
Wait.
It's you.
You've got some nerve!
You even came back here!
Is that all you can do? Here!
- [groaning, grunting]
- [squealing]
Hey! You're slow, boy!
- [grunts and groans]
- [squealing]
[thumping]
[screaming and panicking]
[clamoring]
Let me borrow your slingshot, boss.
[mid-tempo rock music playing]
- [grunting]
- [shrieking]
[grunting]
- [groans]
- [gasps]
[Jona] Denden!
‪Come on.
‪[squaeling]
[Jona] Denden, stay here, stay here.
- [grunting]
- [indistinct]
Not me!
‪-[squealing]
‪-[grunting]
‪[whimpering]
Go ahead!
[grunting and groaning]
- [T-Bak] Okay, okay, huh!
- [clamoring]
[Uno] What? Okay, huh?
[clamoring]
[T-Bak] Grab the gun!
Okay! Okay!
[music fades]
[man] Don't move!
‪[suauve theme music playing]
[grunts and groans]
[grunting and muttering]
- [Emerson] What?
- [man] You!
Admit it.
You kidnapped Atoy, didn't you?!
[Jona] Are you the reason he disappeared?!
I don't know what you're talking about!
You're a fool, bro. Oh.
Better take these guys to the town hall.
[Nestor] Yes.
[Emerson] These guys
will just cause trouble here.
- [Uno] Remember their faces.
- Hey--
Do you know how to speak English?
- Can you speak English?
- Are you okay? Were you hurt? Or…
- Answer!
- [light music laying]
I'm fine.
You, were you hurt?
[Tukmol, in English] You have the right
to remain silent!
- [in English] Anything you say can--
- I'm fine.
[Tukmol, in English] Anything
you say can you--
Hey, flirt later, huh.
Uno, maybe you can call
your Boss Mercado first.
Atoy needs him now.
Okay, later then, huh.
[indistinct chattering]
[light music playing]
[music fades]
Okay, okay. Update me.
[Mongki, in English] Boss.
What? Did they see Audrey?
[in English] Negative.
Our men saw nothing in Tabang Lupa.
They're still at the precinct now.
Add more men.
Maybe Audrey just slipped past them.
I think your sister sensed it.
And your son too.
That's why they left that place.
Our boys also said
Atoy is missing.
Missing how?
Our men are being accused
of kidnapping Atoy.
But they don't know anything!
Maybe you ordered someone else, boss.
[pensive music playing]
I wish we were the ones who kidnapped him.
But whoever did it, I hope…
I hope they kill Atoy.
[tense music playing]
Less problems for us.
[music swells and fades]
Brother Jesus.
Please bring Tatoy home.
Please make him stronger too.
Because his voice seemed weak earlier.
Send your angels to him.
And give him superpowers to help him.
Amen.
[melancholic music playing]
Hey.
What are you doing?
So, you were just there all this time.
This is for me and Mama.
This big dog, she's Mama.
And I'm the puppy.
[gentle music playing]
That works…
She's just one,
but when they're put together again,
they're smiling at each other.
Let me see.
[music fades]
[in English] Corny!
[somber music playing]
Janine!
You're starting to bully me again.
Because…
Because it looks ugly!
I didn't make this to impress you.
Janine, you know what a humble pie is?
You should eat that, so you'd be humble.
About…
[in English] One hundred slices!
[mocking] Whatever. You're still corny!
But I'm serious.
Shouldn't you be nice already?
Especially since so many bad things
have happened to your family.
Gosh! What's the connection?
You just want to say something!
I mean, our lives can change suddenly.
Before, you were free.
Now, you have to hide from your Uncle Red.
Why would I listen to you?
[pensive music playing]
And this?
This Sister Tonet of yours?
She's ugly!
There you go again, Janine!
This is Sister Tonet.
Do you want her to haunt you?
Huh? She made her presence felt before!
I don't believe you.
Suit yourself!
[music fades]
[somber music playing]
[sneaky music playing]
Miss, what did they say?
Will they save Atoy?
Yes. He's talking to his boss inside.
They said they'll send an extraction team.
I'll talk to Boss Mercado first.
I need to be on that team
so we can strike back hard for Atoy.
Wait, wait.
Didn't they send me out
because they had something
confidential to discuss?
Stay here.
You know, I think their boss won't allow
civilians to be involved.
Especially if they're
wimpy, softy.
[in English] Wow.
[smirks]
Wimpy, softy. Me?
[in English] Come on.
Wow! What do you think I am, a pillow?
- Boiled?
- [quirky sting]
Even if you slam my head on wood,
the wood will break.
What I mean is,
someone without experience in
ground combat.
I heard about
that Viktor Petrov.
The one said to have captured Atoy.
Isn't he involved
in a major terrorist group?
Oh, so? Do you think you can fight him?
[Cita] Mmm, see.
Olga is right.
In short, don't meddle
in Uno's and Mercado's plan!
They'll just worry about you!
- That's harsh, miss.
- Oh?
At least side with me here,
even just a little.
You're all so rough on me.
You know, if Uno should bring anyone
to their operations…
[smirks]
…it should be me. Okay?
And, also, he wouldn't just
rush in, charge at them,
and start shooting just like that, right?
Of course, he'd enter cautiously.
They'd want to get inside
without anyone noticing.
That's how it is! You know, I once worked
as an extra in an indie film.
It was exactly like that.
That was the style.
But we were in disguise.
Oh-- Impressive! You have a point.
Right?
You should suggest that to Uno, okay?
That would be a big help.
Wait, wait, wait. I'll talk to him first.
What he needs is a real tough backup.
Not extras from a movie, ehem.
[Emerson clears throat]
Ugh.
- And as a fatter of mact…
- [quirky sting]
[both] Huh?
Atoy wouldn't be able to do
these missions if I didn't help him.
This isn't the first time
I've assisted him
in his dangerous missions, you know?
[smirks, in English] And FYI.
[in English] For your inconvenience.
Atoy's missions wouldn't be successful
without my help.
Hmm, okay!
Yes. He even believes in me
more than I believe in myself.
- Okay, fine. That's your story.
- [quirky sting]
But me, I have training in…
fighting skills.
I can act. I can improvise!
Right? Let's just see who gets chosen
between the two of us, because
it looks like only one will win.
[tense music playing]
Okay, fine.
But in my heart,
you're still the winner.
[in English] As always, my love.
‪[quirky sting]
- [eerie music playing]
- [Ibyang] Janine…
What is it?
[Ibyang] Janine, wake up.
I'm Sister Tonet.
[music swells]
Be good
to Ibyang!
- [screams]
- [playful music playing]
[in English] Mommy!
[Janine, in English] Mommy! Mommy! Mommy!
[in English] Mommy, Mommy!
- [in English] Mommy! Mommy! [screams]
- Janine. Janine, Janine!
- Wake up! Wake up.
- What's happening here?!
[sneaky music playing]
Child, are you okay?
- [in English] Mommy, Mommy.
- [in English] What-- What happened?
[Ibyang] I don't know.
Janine suddenly
screamed when I woke up.
- [gasping] Huh?
- [whimpering]
Mommy, I saw
the picture of Sister Tonet
floating in the air.
She's haunting me, Mommy.
And she said something to me.
[Audrey] Um… [sighs]
Really? Maybe
it's because we were talking
about her earlier.
What did she say to you?
Mommy, just sleep with me.
- Child, maybe
- [in English] Please?
you were just dreaming?
Are you sure you saw a picture
floating in the air?
Yes.
I really saw the picture of Sister Tonet.
[sneaky music playing]
[Ibyang] Janine, whatever
Sister Tonet told you,
you should do it.
Child, I think you need to drink water.
Let's go downstairs first.
[music fades]
[knocks on door]
Ibyang.
Can I talk to you
before I let Janine in here?
[sneaky music playing]
Do you want to tell me something?
Um…
- [in English] Good night, sweet dreams.
- [quirky sting]
Aside from good night?
About what happened to Janine?
[music fades]
The floating picture?
Hmm?
You know, I was never close
to your Sister Tonet.
But I think
she wouldn't like that you're using her
to prank Janine.
Sorry, Aunt Audrey.
I'm just annoyed with Janine.
I'm actually nice to her.
But she threw away what I made for Mama.
Don't worry. I'll talk to her.
What was it
that you made for your mama?
Can I see it?
[gentle music playing]
[Ibyang] Here.
[Audrey] This is so cute.
[chuckles softly]
Hmm.
Your mother is really lucky to have you.
You're truly kind, Ibyang.
I'm the lucky one because
I've dreamed for so long
of finding my mama.
[in English] I'm so happy for you, Ibyang.
Pray for me, huh.
That hopefully…
I'll also find what's missing in me.
What is it?
Weren't you happy,
even if your child was fake?
Your life had purpose.
Where is my real child?!
[Audrey sobbing]
Who is she?!
- [sobs]
- [clicks tongue]
[in English] I'll never tell you.
Even if you shoot me.
[melodramatic music playing]
Whatever it is you're looking for,
I'm sure you'll find it too.
[Audrey chuckles]
So don't be sad anymore.
Smile.
[chuckles]
[music fades]
Miss,
please take care of Ibyang.
Don't worry about her.
Many people will look after her here.
Just come back.
There are things you need to face and fix.
I'll handle this.
Child, Mama will leave for now.
You behave here.
[somber music playing]
Please be careful.
Bring my Tatoy home.
[pensive music playing]
When you return,
we'll reunite them again,
so they'll be happy again.
Ibyang.
I love you.
Don't forget that, huh.
I love you too.
But why are you sad?
- You're crying.
- Oh.
No. Oh, no. It's just…
[sniffles]
[in English] Tears of joy.
Um…
[inhales]
[exhales] Anyway…
[melodramatic music playing]
When I return, your life will change.
Whoever holds this…
will make you happy
because that's your family.
What do you mean?
Just trust me, okay?
All right.
I'll go now.
Okay.
[sobs]
[sentimental music playing]
All right. [sniffles]
[music fades]
[traffic humming]
The food here is really good, bro.
Ah, yes. But later,
I'll take care of things.
The two bottles are on me, hmm!
- Really?
- Yes!
- [line rings]
- Okay, I'll cover the bar chow!
- Positive. The two are here.
- Sisig, sisig.
Oh, all right, all right.
[mid-tempo rock music playing]
- There, just at the corner.
- Great!
[footsteps approaching]
Oh. What's that?
[Uno] Oh?
Oh, so? How are you?
Are the truck loader's driver
and helper really there?
It seems like they're not.
You even took longer.
Our intel is reliable,
and I saw them there, eating.
Let's just wait.
Maybe they're not done yet.
My God!
They're taking so long to eat!
I've been retouching my makeup
over and over. I'm feeling sticky!
I'm like
a dish in an eatery that's gone cold,
with flies on it.
I'm about to rot, almost!
You're unbelievable.
So slow.
- [sighs]
- Olga, take your position.
- They're here.
- Huh?
They're here.
[gasps, mutters]
Huh?
[sighs]
[in English] Oh my God!
[in English] My car!
- [in English] Hi, Miss Beautiful!
- Something's smoking!
Did your car overheat?
[sighs]
Yes.
That's easy, ma'am. We'll take care of it.
Huh?!
That's embarrassing.
It's okay, brother.
Um, I can just call a mechanic
if I'm bothering you.
It's embarrassing.
No, we know how.
- We even have the complete tools.
- Really?
They're just in the car truck loader.
Car truck loader? You drive that?
- [gasps]
- Yes.
Really?! Wow!
Where is it? Where's--
There. It's still parked.
There? Where exactly?
- Where?
- At the junkyard!
By the extension.
This is easy to fix.
Ah, really?
Jaymark, get the tools.
- Ah, okay.
- Okay, ma'am.
Should I open it, brother?
[sneaky music playing]
[in English] Excuse me.
Oh, oops! I dropped it.
[thumps, then thuds]
Dropped it.
You're peeking, bro.
[gasps, grunts]
[mid-tempo rock music playing]
Beautiful, right?
Get in!
[music fades]
[tense music playing]
[Samir, in English] Let's go! Hurry,
hurry! Pick them up.
[Lily] What are you doing?
Where are you taking us?
- [in English] Stand them. Stand them up.
- [Lily] Where are you taking us?
[in English] Let's go. Stand them up.
[gasping]
- [both] Stand up.
- [Lily grunts]
[Lily] Where are you taking us?
[in English] Didn't I tell you that today
is the day you'll die?
[in English] And I'm a man of my word!
[in English] So, prepare to die. Let's go!
[in English] What are we waiting for?
- [in English] Bring them. Let's go!
- [Lily] Atoy, what now, Atoy?
[Lily sobs] Don't kill us.
Have mercy on us.
[intense music playing]
Oh, sir! Wait!
[grunts and groans]
UP NEXT
[in English] Gunshots. You two, stay here.
- [grunting]
- [Lily gasps]
[grunting and groaning]
- [grunts and groans]
- Help!
That thing is really going to explode!
That thing is really going to fire.
[T-bak wails]
[grunts and groans]
["Mr. Tailor" playing]
♪ Like a bubble, like a bubble ♪
♪ If the cutter knows where to hit ♪
[music swells]
♪ Fix it ♪
Subtitle translation by: Rachel C. Arias